keh.com 2018-12-22

# Privacy Policy at KEH Camera Store

Unfortunately your current device does not have features required to fully protect your sensitive data while shopping online. In order to protect your own security, we do not allow the placing of orders using insecure devices. To become our valued customer, please upgrade your Internet browser software to a more recent and secure version. We recommend using the latest version of [Google Chrome](https://www.google.com/chrome/browser/desktop/index.html) or [Mozilla Firefox](https://www.mozilla.org/en-US/firefox/new/), but any modern browser will enable you to shop with us. For additional information please feel free to contact our customer support on [ __](tel:1-800-342-5534)[ 1-800-342-5534 ](tel:+1-800-342-5534 "KEH Phone number") . 

At KEH Camera, we understand and share your concern about privacy. KEH Camera treats your personal information with the highest standards of safety, security, and confidentiality. Below is an explanation of our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. If you have questions regarding this policy you may direct them to webmaster@keh.com.

## What type of information does KEH Camera collect?

KEH Camera is committed to providing a safe and enjoyable shopping experience. When we collect information about you it is in an effort to make our products and services more efficient and customized to you. You can browse the KEH Camera website without revealing any personal information about yourself. However, once you give us your personal information you become a valued KEH Camera customer.

Automatic Information __
     Like many retailers we automatically track certain information based upon your behavior on our site. We use this information to analyze our users' behavior, interests, and demographics to better understand and serve our shoppers. This information may include the URL that you just came from, which URL you next go to, what browser you are using, and your IP address.
Personally Identifiable Information __
     This is information that you provide to us that is specific to you. We collect information such as your name, phone number, billing information, shipping information, and other personal information as indicated on the forms throughout our site. You provide such information when you make a purchase, enter a contest or sweepstakes, fill out a survey or form, provide ratings or testimonials feedback, give or redeem a gift certificate, etc. You can always choose not to provide information but you may not be able to use a particular service or feature.
What about Cookies? __
     "Cookies" are small pieces of information that a web site will store on your computer’s hard drive. KEH Camera will use cookies to identify you during your session, make our services easier to use, and to store items in your shopping cart between visits. Cookies are never used to store sensitive customer information such as names, addresses, credit card numbers, or passwords. Acceptance of cookies is not a requirement to browse our site; however our shopping cart does require the acceptance of cookies to work properly. If you would like to place an order on our site but object to or otherwise are unable to use cookies, please call our sales department at 800-342-5534.

## How KEH Camera uses your information

We use the information we collect to improve our products and services and make your shopping experience more efficient. We review the actions of our visitors on an aggregate basis to determine customers' preferences. KEH Camera conducts analysis and research on our visitors' demographics, interests, and pages viewed based on the information provided to us during ordering, from our server log files, contests, or surveys.

Contests and Sweepstakes __
     When you enter a contest or other promotion we may ask you for contact information such as your name, address, and email address in order to administer the contest, to send you promotional emails, notify winners, and make the winners' list publicly available pursuant to certain states' laws. Your consent to such promotional use and disclosure of this information is a condition of your participation. As a condition of receiving any prize you will be required to complete, execute, and return an Affidavit of Eligibility, a Liability Release, and where lawful, a Publicity Release for us to ensure that you are eligible to receive the prize according to the Contest Rules. In cases where the sweepstakes or promotional offer is co-branded with or sponsored by another party, we may share your information with your consent to that party.
Emails __
     It is possible to register a KEH Camera email subscriber directly from our site or through another source such as a sweepstakes, etc. hosted on another site. Upon registering, we will periodically send you newsletters and emails featuring exclusive sales, promotions, and other member-only benefits. If you make a purchase on our site we will send you order and shipping confirmation emails. If you are a subscribed member we will also send you emails to collect ratings and testimonial feedback related to your purchase. If you'd rather not receive emails please email webmaster@keh.com to change your preferences.
Gift Certificates __
     If you purchase a gift certificate on our site we will ask you to provide the recipient's name and email address. The recipient information you provide will only be used to deliver the gift certificate and for no other purpose.

## Does KEH Camera share the information it receives?

The following describes some of the ways that your personally identifiable information may be disclosed:

Fulfillment __
     During the purchasing process we will share your information with certain intermediaries (e.g. UPS, FedEx, credit card processors, product manufacturers, etc.) strictly to process and ship your order.
Agents __
     We employ other third parties to perform services or functions on our behalf in order to improve our site, merchandising, marketing and promotional efforts, communications, or other services. Those third parties include authorized contractors, consultants, and other companies working with us (collectively, "agents"). They only have access to personal information needed to perform their functions and may not share any personal information with others or use it for any other purpose than improving KEH’s services and offerings.
Advertisers __
     We work with third party advertising companies such as Google, Yahoo, etc. to serve and track our ads. These third parties may serve other cookies.
Third Party Sites __
     You may visit other web sites through links on our site that may collect, use, and share your personal information in accordance with their own privacy policies. The information practices of those websites linking from or to our site are not covered by this Policy and we encourage you to be very cautious before you disclose your personal information to others. It is possible that KEH Camera could merge with or be acquired by another business entity. Should such an event occur you should expect that KEH Camera would share some or all of your information in order to continue to provide such products and services.
Legal Requests __
     KEH Camera will cooperate with law enforcement inquiries. KEH Camera reserves the right to disclose any activities or information about you to law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, determine necessary or appropriate, in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, or other activity that is illegal or may expose us or you to legal liability.
Accessing and Updating Your Information __
     You always have the opportunity to review and change the information you provide to us by logging into the site and entering in the new information yourself. You can edit your name, contact information, and preferences by logging into the My Account section of the site.

As a customer, subscriber, or contest entrant, you will occasionally receive e-mail communications about new KEH Camera products, special offers we think you'll like, and requests for feedback. If you want to stop receiving our emails or to specify the communications you prefer to receive you may unsubscribe or edit your profile at any time. You can do this through any of our emails, by visiting your account preferences page, or by sending us an email at webmaster@keh.com. You may ask to have your account information removed from our active databases; however, because we keep track of past purchases you cannot delete information associated with past purchases. Such information will be deactivated as soon as reasonably possible based on your account activity. Also, as a security measure we "back up" the data stored on our systems and such prior information cannot be completely removed from our databases. Therefore, you should not expect that all of your personally identifiable information will be completely removed from our databases in response to your requests.

## Security

The KEH Camera Security Pledge protects you while you shop at KEH Camera so that you never have to worry about credit card safety. KEH Camera's servers use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), an encryption technology that works with Firefox, Microsoft Internet Explorer, and Google Chrome so that only KEH CAMERA can read a buyer's personal information. We reveal only the last four digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. However, we will transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing.

A special note about children's privacy __
     You must be at least 18 years old to have our permission to use this site. We do not knowingly collect, use, or disclose personally identifiable information about visitors under 18 years of age. If you are a minor you can use this service only in conjunction with your parents or guardians.
Privacy Policy Changes __
     KEH Camera reserves the right to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this Policy at any time. Any changes will be posted in this document and will become effective immediately upon being posted unless otherwise stated.
Contacting KEH Camera __
     If you have further questions about KEH Camera’s Privacy Policy or comments on how we can improve the KEH Camera shopping experience please do not hesitate to email us at webmaster@keh.com. If you need more help you can refer to our Help Center or email one of our customer service representatives at customerservice@keh.com. 

You may also write to us at:

KEH Camera, Inc.  
Attn: Webmaster  
4900 Highlands Parkway SE  
Smyrna, GA 30082
